Contact

Jl. Merpati No.79 Condongcatur, Depok, Sleman, Yogyakarta 082243374043 (Mobile) yanuaraditia@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yanuaraditia (LinkedIn) yanuaraditia.com (Personal) paparkir.com (Company) baleritaflorist.com (Company)

Top Skills

Web Design
User Interface Design
Template Design

Languages

English (Limited Working)

Javanese (Native or Bilingual)

Yanuar Aditia

Work Hard Pray Hard

Summary

Experienced Chief Technology Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the utilities industry. Skilled in User Interface Design, Front-end Development, Web Design, Template Design, and Database Administration. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Informatics from Universitas Amikom Yogyakarta.

Experience

Paparkir Chief Technology Officer January 2019 - Present Yogyakarta Province, Indonesia

From Zero To Hero

Paparkir
Co-Founder
December 2017 - Present
Yogyakarta Area, Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Balerita Florist Web Developer November 2019 - December 2019 (2 months) Banten Province, Indonesia

Forum Asisten
Computer Lab Assistant
September 2018 - January 2019 (5 months)
Yogyakarta Province, Indonesia

Ikatan Mahasiswa Kebumen Amikom Web Developer January 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 9 months) Yogyakarta Province, Indonesia Badan Kependudukan dan Keluarga Berencana Nasional (National Population and Family Planning Board)
Freelance Writer
November 2014 - December 2014 (2 months)

Kebumen, Central Java

SMP Negeri 2 Karanggayam Library Technician March 2014 - May 2014 (3 months) Kebumen, Central Java

Education

University of Amikom

Bachelor's degree, Informatics · (2016 - 2020)

Komputer Vocational High School High School Diploma, Information Technology · (2014 - 2016)